{
    "id": "22e60de8e0894e3fbc6d7f5dce3e0d15",
    "title": "Confusing Words Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She is ………………….. of her success.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "confident",
                "confidant"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b0187e480d6b481e85b3ca598e204329"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t want any …………………… explanation.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "further",
                "farther",
                "farthest"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "97e908fae36f46f3a3f22ecca1faecbc"
        },
        {
            "question": "Is there ………………… . in the class?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "anyone",
                "no one",
                "someone"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8a6f1b3281514e849a350026065c5b5d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctor …………………. the patients to quit smoking.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "advised",
                "adviced"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "68b5f34e480b465b9ba541be008b9b9b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He says he is enjoying his …………………… job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "later",
                "latter",
                "latest"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "90d49b668f3e4079b2349c73c8002420"
        },
        {
            "question": "All students should have …………………… .. to a good library.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "access",
                "axis",
                "excess"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0f199da282614c889a76cb36e89b433e"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… football, he plays cricket.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Beside",
                "Besides",
                "Till"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1b06675a886d4bf48d5c93bbdc818f6a"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… knowledge is a dangerous thing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "A little",
                "Little",
                "The little"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d1484c8d218647e8b03cbc369808298d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is my …………………… brother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "elder",
                "older",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c6fe6e38e4e74914a472e0a8cc7e5d07"
        },
        {
            "question": "The sun …………………… .. in the east.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "raises",
                "rises",
                "races"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d04e04a41b2148649649cffe11b33387"
        }
    ]
}